Moses.
They all declared contemptuously that his stories about Sugar Candy Mountain were lies.
And yet, they allowed him to remain on the farm not working with an allowance
of a gill of beer a day.
After his hoof had healed up, Boxer worked harder than ever.
Indeed, all the animals worked like slaves that year.
Apart from the regular work of the farm and the rebuilding of the windmill,
there was the schoolhouse for the young pigs which was started in March.
Sometimes the long hours on insufficient food were hard to bear. But Boxer never faltered.
In nothing that he said or did was there any sign that his strength was not what
it had been.
It was only his appearance that was a little altered.
His hide was less shiny than it had used to be and his great haunches seemed to
have shrunken.
The others said, >> "Boxer will pick up when the spring grass comes on."
>> But the spring came and Boxer grew no fatter.
Sometimes on the slope leading to the top of the quarry, when he braced his
muscles against the weight of some vast boulder, it seemed that nothing kept him
on his feet except the will to continue.
At such times, his lips were seen to form the words, >> "I will work harder."
>> He had no voice left.
Once again, Clover and Benjamin warned